

SHIRALIYEV ALİ

Front End Developer

About Me

I have worked in many jobs.
I know many areas for this. I would recommend you to try me in your company. It would be my pleasure to



work with you +48-514-071-521 +994-70-366-02-96



shireliyevali@gmail.com



Ksiakowa 9f, Warshaw



https://github.com/Alex260619 84

LANGUAGE

- English (B2)
- French (B2)
- Polish (B1)
- Russian (B2)
- Turkish (C1)

EXPERTISE

- Word
- Excell
- HTML, CSS, Java Script,
 Type Script, Bootstrap,
 React, Angular
- Connecting devices
- Formatting computers
- Repair of computers

EXPERIENCE

Avtoservis LLC 2007-2008

Plumbing engineer of buildings

Design Glass LLC 2008-2011

Operator (in the bottle packing machine)

Azeripmapservis LLC 2011-2013

Dispatcher (repairing oil wells)

Engin LLC 2014-2015

Merchandiser (Procter and Gamble products)

Municipality 2015-2016

Computer operator, cashier

Azkron LLC Khazar Automobile Plant 2018-2021

Master - on the assembly of cars

Kebab King 2021

Master chef

EDUCATION

Azerbaijan University of Languages (bachelor) 2002 - 2006